Some people can never believe in themselves, until someone believes in them.
Good Will Hunting is a drama film directed by Gus Van Sant.
Will Hunting is a headstrong, working-class genius
who is failing the lessons of life.
After one too many run-ins with the law, Will's last chance is a
psychology professor, who might be the only man who can reach him.
Will Hunting, played by Matt Damon.
Sean Maguire, played by Robin Williams.
Chuckie Sullivan, played by Ben Affleck.
Gerald Lambeau, played by Stellan Skarsgård.
Skylar, played by Minnie Driver.
Morgan O'Mally, played by Casey Affleck.
Good Will Hunting is a 1997 American drama film directed by Gus
Van Sant and written by Ben Affleck and Matt Damon.
It stars Robin Williams, Damon, Affleck, Stellan Skarsgård and Minnie Driver.
The film tells the story of janitor Will Hunting, whose
mathematical genius is discovered by a professor at MIT.
The film received acclaim from critics and grossed over $225 million
during its theatrical run against a $10 million budget.
At the 70th Academy Awards, it received nominations in nine categories, including Best Picture and Best Director, and
won in two: Best Supporting Actor for Williams and Best Original Screenplay for Affleck and Damon.
In 2014, it was ranked at number 53 in The Hollywood
Reporter's "100 Favorite Films" list.
The film explores themes of boston, massachusetts,
mathematics, genius, male friendship, flashback.
The tone is emotional.